<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Acarya</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="image"> Exercise Image</string>
    <string name="finish">Redirect To Home</string>
    <string name="date_and_time_of_your_past_workout">Date and Time of your past workouts :</string>
    <string name="your_selected_time_appears_here">Your Selected Time Appears here</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_app"># Acarya
 An App made for Changing your lifestyle


### Problem Statement
People nowadays are more concerned with their work than with their health. Approximately 75% of the population has an unhealthy lifestyle. Indias Happiness Index score has been declining, with one of the main reasons being an unhealthy lifestyle. We all understand how vital it is to be healthy and live in peace with our families and ourselves, to eat whatever we like, and to incorporate exercise into our daily routine.

### Proposed Solution
Our objective is to assist people with the importance of health, how they may improve their health in todays hectic world, and what efforts they should take to maintain their health. They can complete the 10-minute workout by following the steps given. It will serve as a daily reminder. People will be reminded to stay hydrated, and they will be able to review their training history. Also, assess your BMI and set a diet alarm for yourself (Diet alarms are under-development).\n \t

### Functionality and concepts used: -
The app offers a user interface that is both simple and interactive. The following are a few Android principles that were used to achieve the app\'s functionalities. -

#### Constraint Layout : Most of the activities in the app uses a flexible constraint layout, which is easy to handle for different screen sizes.

#### Bottom Navigation Menu : The App Implements Bottom Navigation Menu using fragments in a single activity using Jetpack Navigation component.

#### SQLite Database : The App Implements the SqliteOpenHelper class and stores the workout history of the user.

####Text-to-Speech : The App also Implements the text to speech Functionality for narrating the exercise name.

#### RecyclerView : The app Implements RecyclerView twice. Once to keep the track of exercises during workout and then to display the workout history of the user."

    App Developers : Yash Grover , Utkarsh Singh
    Other Contributions : Prerna Dhiman , Lakshya Dhawan , Jahnvi Pandey ,Abhishek Tyagi , Arpit Verma</string>
</resources>